// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answer
let questions= [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "In a certain code language PAYMENT is coded as 6101814111520 and JUSTIFY is coded as 11141519151620. How will COMPARE be coded in that language?",
        answer: 681013101113,
        options: [680113111103,                                        
        601811031131,
        613101113801,
        681013101113
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Four Letter-clusters have been given, out of which three are alike in some manner and one is different. Select the letter-clusters that is different.",
        answer: "SHLO",
        options: ["KPSH",
        "JQTG",
        "SHLO",
        "DWZA"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In a certain code language, RAJ is coded as 87 and GITA is coded as 148. How will VARUN be coded in that language?",
        answer: 380,
        options: [176,
        234,
        403,
        380
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "In a certain code language, PERMIT is written as VVLNOG  How will INERTIA be written in that language?",
        answer: "OMYIZRU",
        options: ["OHYXZCU",
        "XOYHCZU",
        "OMYIZRU",
        "XYOHBCU"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Four Letter-clusters have been given, out of which three are alike in some manner and one is different. Select the letter-clusters that is different.",
        answer: "HJMP",
        options: ["LNOJ",
        "BDGT",
        "HJMP",
        "TVYB"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "In a certain code language, VIRTUE is coded as 201 and TRAGEDY is coded as 218. How will PROFANE be coded in that language?",
        answer: 342,
        options: [570,
        342,
    456,
    432
]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Four number-pairs have been given, out of which three are alike in some manner and one is different. Select the number-pairs that is different.",
        answer: "15 : 197",
        options: ["21 : 139",
            "25 : 167",
            "15 : 197",
           "27 : 181"
            ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Select the number from among the given options that can replace the question mark(?) in the following series: 10, 22, 35, 40, 72, 40, ?",
        answer: 133,
        options: [134,
        143,
        131,
        133
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "In a certain code language, PLIGHTH is written as JMQUIH. How will CANDLE be written in that language?",
        answer: "OBDFME",
        options: ["ODBFME",
            "OBDFME",
            "OBDFEM",
            "BODMFE"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "If 19 July 2000 was a Wednesday, then what would be the day of the week on the 15 June 2012?",
        answer: "Friday",
        options: ["Friday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Thursday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    }
]